a.
First it defines a global variable 'x' with value 1. Then it 
creatres a constant 'foo' which is assigned to an arrow function. The arrow function changes the value
of the global variable x to 2, then it returns another arrow 
function that log the current value of x on the screen. foo()()
calls the function foo, which returns a function, so the second
pair of parentesis call that function inside the return which 
logs on console the current value of x, which is two at this
moment (after foo changes it). Then it logs the global variable
x which is 2. The result is:
2
2

==============
b.
Two arrays are created. Array "items" with 3 values [1,2,3] and 
array result that is empty. It runs a loop that works 3 times 
(for i =0, =1, =2, when i changes to 3 the loop breaks). Each 
time it pushes an arrow function () => items[i] to the result 
array. Since i is declared as 'var' it means it is function
scoped, so it is shared across all interations. After the loop 
the array results is:
results = [() => items[i], () => items[i], () => items[i]]
during the scope of var all three functions refers to the same
i, which is 3 now that the loop ended.
The last line will log on the console the mapping of the result
array. So for each element 'x' inside result it will log 'x()', 
aka the execution of the functions. The three of them are items[3]
now. But items array only goes from index 0 to 2, so this call
results on "undefined", so it will log on the console:
[undefined, undefined, undefined]

=============
c.
If var was changed to let now the i would be block-scoped which
means that each interation of the loop will have its own i. So each
function pushed into result will capture the current value of i.
After the loop the array results is:
results = [() => items[0], () => items[1], () => items[2]]
So now the mapping will excute diferently. It will log on the con-
sole first the element on index 0 of items, the index 1, then index
2., so it will log on the console:
[1,2,3]

=============
d.This is similar to the above, but the content inside the for
loop. the expression that is pushed ((x) => () => items[x])(i)
is an IIFE, Immediately Invoked Function Expression, which is 
marked by wrapping a function definition in parentheses and 
then immediately invoking it with a second set of parenteses.
So for the first iteration of the loop i=0 and it is passed to
invoke the function items[x] with x being i. So () => items[0] 
is pushed to array result. the same happens at second and third 
iteration, at the end result is:
results = [() => items[0], () => items[1], () => items[2]]
which gives the same result as letter c does, even with a var 
declaration, because it is immediately evoked.



